A Guide to the Richmond (Va.), Bureau of Permits and Inspections, Building permit architectural blueprints and specifications, 1907-1976
Library of Virginia
- Blueprint drawings, 1907-1950, 3167 sets of blueprints
  - Residences-single and multi-family dwellings 1909-1948
    - Residence - Permit Number: 9886, Brick Residence for Mr. Littleton Fitzgerald No. 4001 Seminary Ave., Address: 3913 Seminary Ave. (Inspector's address), 1922 (Folder 690)
      Drawn by: I. T. Skinner; Contractor: O. C. Peers; Commissioned by: Littleton Fitzgerald; Notes: Two story Colonial Revival house with a porte cochere, double chimneys and three pedimented dormers which match the pediment of the front entrance porch.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 9277, Brick Residence for Mr. W. W. Roundtree, 3613 Seminary Ave., Ginter Park, Address: 3613 Seminary Ave., 1922 (Folder 421)
      Drawn by: Davis Bros., Inc., Designers and Builders; Contractor: Davis Bros. Inc.; Commissioned by: W. W. Roundtree; Notes:
    - Residence - Permit Number: 9254, Six Houses & Store Nos. 800 - 02 - 04 - 06 - 08 - 10 - 12 - 14 Cleveland St., Address: 802 - 814 Cleveland St., 1922 (Folder 420)
      Drawn by: I. T. Skinner, Architect, Richmond, Va.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: H. C. Brown; Notes:
    - Residence - Permit Number: 10394, Residence for W.W. Workman, Address: 2801 Semmes Ave., 1922 (Folder 783)
      Drawn by: A. Carl Messerschmidt; Contractor: R. M. Anderson; Commissioned by: W. W. Workman; Notes: Two-story, Dutch Colonial Revival, brick house with porte cochere on one side and a two-story, enclosed projection on the opposite side.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 9265, Residence for M. L. Hubbard, Esq., Address: 506 N. Boulevard, 1922 (Folder 425)
      Drawn by: W. Duncan Lee, Architect, 708 Travelers Building, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: M. L. Hubbard Construction; Commissioned by: M. L. Hubbard; Notes:
    - Residence - Permit Number: 10683, Residence for Mr. R. Tyler English, Address: 4200 Seminary Ave., 1922 (Folder 872)
      Drawn by: E. E. Burruss for R. M. Anderson & Co., Gen. Contractors; Contractor: R. M. Anderson; Commissioned by: Lewis Ginter Land and Imp. Company; Notes: Frame house with two stories. The second story overhangs the first and features a so-called Dutch Colonial roof.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 9736, House for J. Scott Parish, Esq., Address: 2311 Monument Ave., 1922 (Folder 51)
      Drawn by: William Lawrence Bottomley, Architect, No. 112 E. 55th Street, NYC; Contractor: J. C. Beazley; Commissioned by: J. Scott Parrish; Notes: The central hall is flanked by the dining room and drawing room and the library behind. A garage wing is attached to the left of the house by a row of service rooms that frame an open space. The numerous rooms on the second and third floors include the owner's, daughter's, and son's rooms, two morning rooms, and three servant's rooms.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 10590, Residence for Mrs. W.H. Jenks, Address: 800 Westover Ave., 1922 (Folder 821)
      Drawn by: C. H. Archer; Contractor: C. H. Archer; Commissioned by: Mrs. W.H. Jenks; Notes: Two-story brick Colonial Revival house with tile roof and porte cochere. The louvered shutters on the second story contain a cut-out flower motif in the upper panel. The segmental arch that crowns the central entrance is supported by Doric pilasters.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 9892, Residence for Mrs. J. E. Lewis, Address: 3142 Monument Ave., 1922 (Folder 689)
      Drawn by: W. Duncan Lee; Contractor: Po[sic] and Wilkinson; Commissioned by: Mrs. Mary M. Lewis; Notes: Two story brick Colonial Revival dwelling with a combination gable/hip roof.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 9468, Residence for W.W. Crisp, Address: 3200 Chamberlayne Ave., 1922 (Folder 977)
      Drawn by: P. S. Lubienski; Contractor: P. S. Lubienski; Commissioned by: W. W. Crisp; Notes: Two-story, frame and brick veneer house. The plan is a central block with side projections.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 9176, Residence for Mr. J. H. Britton, Address: 3804 Chamberlayne Ave., 1922 (Folder 693)
      Drawn by: I. T. Skinner; Contractor: O. C. Peers; Commissioned by: J. H. Britton; Notes: Two story brick Colonial Revival house with porte cochere. The central entrance door has a fanlight and is covered by a porch which features a broken Classical pediment supported by Doric columns. The three dormers in the side gable roof repeat the theme of the porch.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 9118, Residence No. 101, Address: 1506 Wilmington Ave., 1922 (Folder 697)
      Drawn by: I. T. Skinner; Contractor: O. J. Davis; Commissioned by: J. D. Carneal; Notes: Two story brick Colonial Revival house with porte cochere and Spanish tile roof. The central entrance is covered with a broken pedimented porch supported by Doric columns.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 9995, Two Family House and Garage, Address: 1411 Wilmington Ave., 1922 (Folder 699)
      Drawn by: Charles M. Robinson; Contractor: R. M. Anderson; Commissioned by: Maud Starke (Mrs. J. E. Warriner); Notes: Two story stucco two family house designed in a Tudor style imitation half timber gables.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 9205, Residence for Mr. H. Rohm, Address: 3505 Chamberlayne Ave., 1922 (Folder 700)
      Drawn by: Bascom J. Rowlett; Contractor: Harry Rohm; Commissioned by: H. Rohm; Notes: Two story brick house with stucco trim. The central plan includes a sun porch and a porte cochere on opposite ends of the front elevation. The tile hip roof includes dormers on the side elevations only.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 10585, Residence for Joseph H. Harrison, Address: 3815 Seminary Ave., 1922 (Folder 827)
      Drawn by: R. M. Anderson; Contractor: R. M. Anderson and Co.; Commissioned by: Joseph H. Harrison; Notes: Two-story, frame house designed in the Colonial Revival style with two side extensions and double chimneys.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 9424, Residence for Milton J. and Irving J. Straus, Address: 2025 Monument Ave., 1922 (Folder 979)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: L. C. Jenkins; Commissioned by: Milton J. and Irving J. Straus; Notes: Two-story, brick Colonial Revival house. The facade is asymmetrical with a side entrance covered by a portico supported by two-story Corinthian columns. Quoin corners, window sills and lintels are built of stone. A floating balcony extends off the second story French doors.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 10592, Two Dwellings for Bellevue Park, Inc., Address: 3219-21 Monument Ave., 1922 (Folder 826)
      Drawn by: Davis Bros., Inc.; Contractor: Davis Bros.; Commissioned by: Bellevue Park, Inc.; Notes: Two, two-story brick houses with double end chimneys and steeply pitched decorative gables on the front facade.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 10682, Muhleman & Kayhoe Buildings, Address: 1602-06-10-14 Palmyra Ave., 1922 (Folder 891)
      Drawn by: W. H. Pringle; Contractor: Muhleman and Kayloe; Commissioned by: Laburnum Corp.; Notes: A set of four separate house plans and elevations to be built by Muhleman & Kayhoe. The two-story houses are designed in a suburban, Colonial Revival style.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 10437, Residence and Garage for Lee A. Whitlock, Address: 3400 Monument Ave., 1922 (Folder 812)
      Drawn by: G. Herbert French; Contractor: A. F. Perrin; Commissioned by: Mrs. Rhonie H. Whitlock; Notes: This house and two others in Richmond are the only Virginia buildings attributed to the little known architect, French, who was active in Richmond from 1916-1924. The present building is a very fine two-story stucco house with a central block flanked by two projections. The side entry door is located under an arched breezeway. The floor-to-ceiling windows on the first story are crowned with Palladian lights giving the facade the appearance of an Italian villa.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 09696, Stucco Residence for Mr. W.T. Shepherd, Address: 1612 Belleview Ave., 1922 (Folder 751)
      Drawn by: Davis Bros., Inc.; Contractor: Davis Bros., Inc.; Commissioned by: Belleview Park Inc.; Notes: Two story stucco Colonial Revival house with hip roof and side projections. The entrance sets asymmetrically on the facade and is covered with a flat roofed porch supported by Doric columns wrapped in stucco.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 10684, Residence To Be Erected by Muhleman & Kayhoe, Address: 1601-5-9-13-17 Confederate Ave., 1922 (Folder 896)
      Drawn by: W. H. Pringle; Contractor: Muhleman and Kayhoe; Commissioned by: Laburnum Corp.; Notes: Five frame residences to be built according to one plan and elevation. The elevation shows a two-story house with a so-called Dutch Colonial roof.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 10324, Brick Residence for S.V. Moody, Address: 3607 Grove Ave., 1922 (Folder 793)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: W. S. Quarles; Commissioned by: S. V. Moody; Notes: Two story brick house with full front porch.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 09481, Frame and Stucco Residence for the Realty & Finance Corp., Address: 3219 Garland Ave., 1922 (Folder 748)
      Drawn by: Realty Finance Corp.; Contractor: Realty Finance Corp.; Commissioned by: Realty Finance Corp.; Notes: Two story stucco and frame house designed in an Arts and Crafts style.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 09773, Two, Two-Story Houses for P.S. Lubienski, Address: 3202-04 Chamberlayne Ave., 1922 (Folder 752)
      Drawn by: P. S. Lubienski; Contractor: P. S. Lubienski; Commissioned by: P. S. Lubienski; Notes: Two, two-story frame and brick veneer Colonial Revival houses.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 9849, Residence for P.S. Lubienski, Address: 2318 Grove Ave., 1922 (Folder 746)
      Drawn by: P. S. Lubienski; Contractor: P. S. Lubienski; Commissioned by: P. S. Lubienski; Notes: Two story brick Colonial Revival house with full front porch supported by coupled, fluted Doric Columns.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 10395, Residence for Lewis Kaufman, Address: 804 Westover Rd., 1922 (Folder 797)
      Drawn by: Otis K. Asbury; Contractor: Lewis Kaufman; Commissioned by: Lewis Kaufman; Notes: Plans and elevations for a substantial residence executed in stucco with a tile roof of various intersecting gables.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 9487, Residence for J. H. Frischkorn, Address: 3212 Monument Ave., 1922 (Folder 958)
      Drawn by: G. Herbert French; Contractor: A. F. Perrin; Commissioned by: J. H. Frischkorn; Notes: Two-story, Colonial Revival house with double chimneys and slate roof. The second story is delineated with two courses of slate which extend upward on the sides toward the roof. The central entrance is flanked by French doors. Each second-story window has wood panel shutters and a flower box.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 10489, Residence for Mr. Edgar Marshall, Address: 2614 Seminary Ave., 1922 (Folder 810)
      Drawn by: C. K. H., Jr. (C.K. Howell ?); Contractor: Edgar Marshall; Commissioned by: Edgar Marshall; Notes: Two-story, stucco, Colonial Revival house designed in a center hall plan with side projections.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 10129, Residence for Col. J.W. Williams, Address: 3104 Monument Ave., 1922 (Folder 799)
      Drawn by: Davis Bros., Inc.; Contractor: Davis Bros.; Commissioned by: J. W. Williams; Notes: Two-story, brick Colonial Revival house with side entry. The first floor windows are crowned with brick arches. The second floor windows have flat arches with keystones and the shutters contain "flower pot" cut-outs in the upper panel.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 9746, Residence for Morgan R. Mills, Address: 2304 Lakeview Ave., 1922 (Folder 743)
      Drawn by: Carneal & Johnston, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: J. W. Atkinson8; Commissioned by: Morgan R. Mills; Notes: Two story, brick Colonial Revival house with open side porch.
    - Residence - Permit Number: N/A, Residence for Charles Rose, Address: 3209 Monument Ave., 1922 (Folder 742)
      Drawn by: R. M. Anderson and Company; Contractor: R. M. Anderson and Company; Commissioned by: Charles Rose; Notes: Two story Colonial Revival house designed and built by R. M. Anderson and Company. Cost and address were obtained from Wells and Dalton, 9. CD # 95.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 9340, Residence for Mr. Walter Christian, Address: 1526 Park Ave., 1922 (Folder 973)
      Drawn by: I. T. Skinner; Contractor: O. J. Davis; Commissioned by: Mrs. Kate N. Christian; Notes: Two-story, brick Colonial Revival house with full front porch and a minor one-story, side projection (enclosed).
    - Residence - Permit Number: 11329, Residence Monument Avenue, Address: 2605 Monument Ave., 1922 (Folder 538)
      Drawn by: W. Duncan Lee; Contractor: J. R. Jones; Commissioned by: Mrs. Jonathan Bryan; Notes: Two-story brick "Tudorbean" style residence with L-shaped plan.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 9844, Two Family House for Mrs. Enslow, Address: 1404 Wilmington Ave., 1922 (Folder 744)
      Drawn by: Richmond Construction Co., Inc.; Contractor: Richmond Construction Co., Inc.; Commissioned by: Mrs. Marie H. Enslow; Notes: Two story Colonial Revival house intended for two families.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 9363, Residence for Mrs. Louise H. Miller, Address: 3001 Grove Ave., 1922 (Folder 976)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: E. L. Bass; Commissioned by: Louise H. Miller; Notes: Two-story, brick Colonial Revival house with full front porch supported by coupled Doric columns that rest on brick pedestals.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 9495, Brick Residence for Mr. Warren M. Goddard, Address: 3317 Monument Ave., 1922 (Folder 966)
      Drawn by: Davis Brothers; Contractor: Davis Bros.; Commissioned by: Warren M. Goddard; Notes: Two-story brick Colonial Revival with side entrance and a two-story side wing. The windows have 6/6 sashes, louvered shutters, and stone sills and keystones in the flat brick arches.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 9702, Residence for C.W. Davis and R.M. Smith, Address: 2701 Grove Ave., 1922 (Folder 740)
      Drawn by: Davis Bros., Inc.; Contractor: Davis Bros., Inc.; Commissioned by: C. W. Davis and R. M. Smith; Notes: Detached brick house "ready for occupancy," this was probably an investment property for C. W. Davis, one of the principals of Davis Bros., Inc.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 9707, Residence (and garage) for Dr. Wyndham B. Blanton, Address: 3015 Seminary Ave., 1922 (Folder 738)
      Drawn by: William C. Noland; Contractor: John E. Dicks; Commissioned by: Dr. W.B. Blanton; Notes: Two story brick Colonial Revival house with center hall plan and open side porch.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 10510, Residence for E.C. Pelouze, Address: 4101 Monument Ave., 1922 (Folder 816)
      Drawn by: Lee & Lee, Architects and Engineers; Contractor: J. R. Jones; Commissioned by: E. C. Pelouze; Notes: Compact, stucco, story-and-a-half house with gambrel roof and porte cochere. Excellent detail of the fan element over the center door is shown. Arched windows are set into broken pediments to form three classical dormers on the front facade.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 9433, Flat Building for Max E. Ruehrmund, Address: 3149 W. Main St., 1922 (Folder 968)
      Drawn by: Max E. Ruehrmund; Contractor: Max E. Ruehrmund; Commissioned by: Max E. Ruehrmund; Notes: Two-story brick building with plans to accommodate four identical flats. The facade is an eclectic mixture of classical elements and materials to include stucco, slate, wood, and brick.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 09808, Residence and Garage for Robert F. Sycle, Address: 3200 Monument Ave., 1922 (Folder 757)
      Drawn by: W. Duncan Lee; Contractor: C. F. Duggins; Commissioned by: Mrs. Fannie Sycle; Notes: Two story brick house designed in an Italian villa revival style
    - Residence - Permit Number: 11534, Five Flat Buildings, Address: 2207 W. Cary St., 1923 (Folder 871)
      Drawn by: Max E. Ruehrmund; Contractor: Max Ruehrmund; Commissioned by: J. H. Mauck and Max E. Ruehrmund (see specifications); Notes: Five brick buildings with individualized facades. Each is designed to house two flats or apartments.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 11445, Residence for Mrs. M. A. Hall, Address: 1610 Confederate Ave., 1923 (Folder 867)
      Drawn by: Lee & Lee; Contractor: Building and Security Corp.; Commissioned by: Mary A. Hall; Notes: Two story cinder block house veneered in brick and stucco. The Colonial Revival, center hall plan includes a minor projection on either side of the front elevation.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 11461, Job 5000 (House), Address: 2120 Lakeview Ave., 1923 (Folder 868)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: Muhleman and Kayhoe; Commissioned by: Jas. G. Roeber; Notes: Although the inspector indicated on the outside of the plans that this is an "apt. building," the plans show a two- story, brick and frame, Colonial Revival house with a so-called Dutch Colonial roof.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 11695, Residence for C. W. Leonard, Address: 1509 Wilmington Ave., 1923 (Folder 850)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: D.A. Weatherford; Commissioned by: C. W. Leonard; Notes: Two-story brick house with central entry covered by a minor porch. The side gable roof contains a decorative, steeply pitched gable on the facade.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 11583, Residence for Mary E. McCarty, Address: 1220 W. Franklin St., 1923 (Folder 873)
      Drawn by: Otis K. Asbury; Contractor: Mary E. McCarty; Commissioned by: Mary E. McCarty; Notes: Two-story, brick, Colonial Revival house with side entrance covered by a porch supported by Doric Columns. The back elevation shows double porches with wood balustrades.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 11505, Brick Dwelling, Address: 3304 Stuart Ave., 1923 (Folder 874)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: A. L. Sharp; Commissioned by: A. L. Sharp; Notes: Two-story, brick Colonial Revival house that features a full front porch and prominent cornice brackets.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 11552, Residence for S. S. Ellett, Address: 4402 Monument Ave., 1923 (Folder 866)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: E. L. Bass; Commissioned by: S. S. Ellett; Notes: Two-story brick Colonial Revival house.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 13063, George H. Adams Residence, Address: 2800 Montrose Ave., 1923 (Folder 1048)
      Drawn by: Geo. H. Adams (drawn by E.E. Burris); Contractor: Geo. H. Adams; Commissioned by: Geo. H. Adams; Notes: 2-story, brick, Colonial Revival house w/finished attic story and wraparound porch. Adams w/listed as a contractor and builder in Richmond in 1913, 1919, and 1924 according to city directories.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 11499, Brick Veneer Residence for Mr. W.O. Perrin, Address: 3009 Hawthorne Ave., 1923 (Folder 865)
      Drawn by: I. T. Skinner; Contractor: O. C. Peers; Commissioned by: W. O. Perrin; Notes: Two-story Colonial Revival house with porte cochere and side porch. The brick chimney is asymmetrically placed on the front elevation to the right of the front entrance.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 11020, Residence for Mrs. S. A. White, Address: 1401 Confederate Ave., 1923 (Folder 1428)
      Drawn by: Davis Bros.; Contractor: Davis Bros.; Commissioned by: Mrs. S. A. White; Notes:
    - Residence - Permit Number: N/A, Eight Brick Dwellings, Address: 3108-3122 Hanover Ave., 1923 (Folder 897)
      Drawn by: Max E. Ruehrmund; Contractor: Max E. Ruehrmund; Commissioned by: Max E. Ruehrmund; Notes: Eight brick dwellings to be built according to the plans and elevations for two separate sets of plans and elevations each of which includes four attached townhouses.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 12561, Residence and Garage for J. S. Cruickshanks, Address: 1614 Wilmington Ave., 1923 (Folder 1111)
      Drawn by: Cruickshanks Iron Works Co. drawn by J.S.C.; Contractor: D. A. Weatherford; Commissioned by: J. S. Cruickshanks; Notes: Two-story, brick house with tile roof and open side terrace. The central arched doorway is covered by a porch supported by Doric columns.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 11625, Mausoleum for Mrs. James H. Dooley To Be Erected At Maymont, Address: Maymont, 1923 (Folder 862)
      Drawn by: Baskervill & Lambert; Contractor: I.J. Smith and Co.; Commissioned by: Mrs. S.M. Dooley; Notes: Stone mausoleum for the sarcophagus of Mrs. James H. Dooley, the wife of the original owner of the Maymont estate. Designed in with Greek elements, the building has bronze doors and a bronze roof grill.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 11521, Residence for Mrs. Charlotte L. Stoakley, Address: 1402 Palmyra Ave., 1923 (Folder 860)
      Drawn by: Lee & Lee; Contractor: Building and Security Company; Commissioned by: Charlotte L. Stoakley; Notes: Two-story, cinder block house designed in the Colonial Revival style with an extension.
    - Residence - Permit Number: N/A, Brick Residence in Douglas Court for Mr. W. A. Jordan, Address: 2602 Brook Rd., 1923 (Folder 1436)
      Drawn by: Charles T. Russell, Architect, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: W. A. Jordan; Notes:
    - Residence - Permit Number: 11722A, Alterations and Additions to 1652 W. Grace St., Address: 1652 W. Grace St., 1923 (Folder 540)
      Drawn by: Marcus Hallet; Contractor: L. C. Rowlett; Commissioned by: W. Withers Miller; Notes: Alterations and additions to a brick and stucco house.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 11284, [Residence], Address: 2910 Chamberlayne Ave,, 1923 (Folder 542)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: M. D. Hurt; Commissioned by: Joseph Perry; Notes: Nine-room, two-story, brick veneer house designed in an Arts and Crafts style.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 11363, [Residence], Address: 2700 Chamberlayne Ave., 1923 (Folder 544)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: W. D. Hurt; Commissioned by: W. D. Hurt; Notes: Nine room, two-story, brick veneer house designed in an Arts & Crafts style
    - Residence - Permit Number: 1060, Residence for J.E. Crass, Address: 900 Westover Rd., 1923 (Folder 839)
      Drawn by: I. T. Skinner; Contractor: O. C. Peers; Commissioned by: J. E. Crass; Notes: Two-story, brick, Colonial Revival house with minor loggias projecting from each side. The central door and first floor windows are topped with fanlights.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 10841, Residence for L. W. Hoffman, Address: 1215 Confederate Ave., 1923 (Folder 904)
      Drawn by: J. Frank Darling & Co.; Contractor: J. Frank Darling and Co.; Commissioned by: L. W. Hoffman; Notes: Two-story over basement dwelling with a center hall plan, a porte cochere at left on the elevation and a two-story enclosed projection at right on the elevation.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 10767, Residence for T. W. Leonard, Address: 3212 W. Franklin St., 1923 (Folder 884)
      Drawn by: C. H. Archer; Contractor: C. H. Archer; Commissioned by: T. W. Leonard; Notes: Two-story, brick Colonial Revival house. The back elevation features double sleeping porches.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 12301, [Residence], Address: 1307 Sauer Ave., 1923 (Folder 18)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: W. S. Quarles; Commissioned by: C. F. Sauer? M. P. Will?; Notes: Two-story and basement brick house with slate roof.
    - Residence - Permit Number: 10941, Two Frame Dwellings, Address: 3909 - 3911 Hermitage Rd., 1923 (Folder 1432)
      Drawn by: C. E. Sprinkle; Contractor: C. E. Sprinkle; Commissioned by: Sallie Alfriend, Real Estate Holding Co.; Notes:
    - Residence - Permit Number: 110056, Brick Dwelling, Address: 1412 Wilmington Ave., 1923 (Folder 1437)
      Drawn by: H. Weber; Contractor: Horace Weber; Commissioned by: Hannah E. Weber; Notes:
    - Residence - Permit Number: 12331, Residence for G.E. Turner, Address: 1609 Wilmington Ave., 1923 (Folder 1016)